Sergeev Roman, Python Backend Developer

Email: rmnsrgeev@gmail.com

Phone: +343434343434 Telegram: @rmzsrb

About me:

Backend developer with 2 years of experience. Wrote in Python. Handled a wide range of tasks from backend development for web and applications, working with APIs, to creating and analyzing databases for various requests. Passionate about sports and keen on exploring new technologies.

Skills

Python, Django, SQL, Asyncio, RestAPI, FastAPI, Postgres, Docker, Git, Scrum, English-B2

Experience

Python backend developer in React.

April 2023 - March 2024

Developed microservices including authentication and authorization services, API gateways, and database management for web applications.

Python backend developer in Ruwater.

February 2022 - March 2023

Developed a sales data analysis system for water products using SQL and PostgreSQL, implementing advanced data querying and manipulation techniques. This involved creating efficient database schemas, writing complex SQL queries, and integrating PostgreSQL functionalities to extract, analyze, and visualize sales trends, customer behavior, and inventory levels to inform strategic decision-making

Experience before professional development

Moko Design Studio

June 2020 - until now

Co-owner of design clothing brand.

Managed organizational activities overseeing internal company processes.

Education

Tymen State Oil Technical University September 2017 - July 2021 Lawyer